Guide to the Anna Fuller Fund Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Anna Fuller Fund records
1931-1984
RU 747
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
17.5
(42 boxes)
The records consist of grant reports, financial records, and correspondence documenting the status and recipients of the Anna Fuller Fund and the Anna Fuller Prize. Included is a photocopy of Egbert C. Fuller's will.
Anna Fuller Fund
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 37 (YRG 37), Records of associations, institutes, centers, and organizations affiliated with Yale University.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Biographical / Historical
The Anna Fuller Fund and Anna Fuller Memorial Prize were established in 1932 by the bequest of Egbert Chaplain Fuller in honor of his wife who died of cancer in 1918. The aim of the fund, as outlined in Fuller's will, is "to alleviate suffering from disease, through: (a) research as to its cause, treatment and care; (b) the education of the public as to its prevention and treatment; and (c) the actual treatment of persons suffering from disease. My chief interest is in the alleviation of suffering from cancer..."
Scope and Contents
The records consist of grant reports, financial records, and correspondence documenting the status and recipients of the Anna Fuller Fund and the Anna Fuller Prize. Included is a photocopy of Egbert C. Fuller's will.
Arrangement
The records are arranged in two series: I. Reports and Miscellaneous Projects. II. Anna Fuller Grants.
Cancer -- Research grants; Cancer -- Research; Medicine -- Awards; Medicine -- Research grants; Medicine -- Research; Fuller, Egbert C. (Egbert Chaplain); Anna Fuller Fund
- Anna Fuller Fund Records, Accession 1988-A-094
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  - Reports and Miscellaneous Projects, Series I
    - Annual Medical Reports, 1935-1947 (Box 1, Folder 1-6)
    - Annual Medical Reports, 1947-1956 (Box 2, Folder 7-10)
    - Annual Medical Reports, 1957-1962 (Box 3, Folder 11-12)
    - Annual Medical Reports, 1969-1984 (Box 4, Folder 13-15)
    - Awards Faculty, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Financial Statement, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Fuller Will, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Index of Grants, 1933-1974, 1950-1961 (Box 5, Folder 19-20)
    - IRS Memorial Prize, 1973-74, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 21 22)
    - O'Gara Memorial, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Anna Fuller Grants, Series II
    - # 2 Memorial Hospital C.P. Rhoads, 1950-1964 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
    - # 8 Chester Beatty Research Institute Alexander Haddow, 1951-1964 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - # 10 Yale University Leanell C. Strong, 1951-1954 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - # 18 Yale University W.U. Gardner, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - # 34 Roscoe B. Jackson Memorial Laboratory C.C. Little, 1951-1964 (Box 6, Folder 6-7)
    - # 39 American Association for Cancer Research, 1951-1966 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - # 44 Rockefeller Institute Eugene L. Opie, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - # 46 University of Maryland Frank H.J. Figge, 1951-1962 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - # 51 Yale University Carroll A. Pfeiffer, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - # 61 Albert Einstein College of Medicine Berta Scharrer, 1951-1955 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - # 62 St. Bartholomew's Hospital Ernest L. Kennaway, 1951-1963 (Box 7, Folder 13-14)
    - # 75 St. Bartholomew's Hospital Ernest L. Kennaway, 1951-1962 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - # 85 University of Copenhagen Julius Engelbreth-Holm, 1951-1957 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - # 88 Brown University Paul L. Fenton, 1950-1959 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - # 90 Chester Beatty Institute, 1952-1962 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - # 94 New York Zoological Society, 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - # 97 Yale University Chu Huai Chang, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - # 98 National Research Council, 1951-1966 (Box 8, Folder 21-22)
    - # 99 Yale University W.T. Salter, 1951-1952 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - # 100 University of Florida F.E. Ray, 1951-1953 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - # 101 Journal of Experimental Zoology J.S. Nicholas, 1951-1955 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - # 103 Yale University Gertrude J. Van-Eck, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - # 104 Washington University Leo Loeb, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - # 105 New England Deaconess Hospital Shields Warren, 1950-1953 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - # 106 University of Ghent Jean J. Boddaert, 1951-1953 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - # 107 University of Puerto Rico C.A. Pfeiffer, 1951-1952 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - # 108 Yale University David E. Morton, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - # 109 New York University Anna Goldfeder, 1951-1956 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - # 111 University of Rochester, 1951-1954 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - # 112 General Grant University of Pennsylvania General Grant, 1951-1956 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - # 113 Washington University Hemprova Ghosh, 1951-1952 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - # 114 New York Zoological Society Racai Ermin, 1951-1952 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - # 115 Peter Bent Brigham Somers H. Sturgis, 1951-1952 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - # 116 American Cancer Society Brewster S. Miller, 1951-1952 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - # 119 Columbia University Charles Ely, 1952-1956 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - # 120 Armed Forces Institute G.H. Klenek, 1952-1964 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - # 121 Yale University Harris Busch, 1952-1953 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - # 123 Yale University E. R. Gabriele, 1952-1953 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - # 124 Boston University Burnham Walker, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - # 125 University of Wisconsin James C. MacDonald, 1954-1956 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - # 126 University of Wisconsin Hans Schmitz, 1953-1957 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - # 127 National Research Council, 1953-1957 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - # 128 University of California J.E. Hotchio, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - # 129 University College Hospital (University of London) Elizabeth Work, 1953-1954 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - # 130 Health Research Incorporated L.C. Strong, 1953-1955 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - # 131 American Association of---Cancer Research. VI International Cancer Congress, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - # 132 International Congress of Clinical Pathology, 1954-1955 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - # 133 St. Bartholomew's Hospital R.E. Waller, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - # 134 McGill University Yves Clermont, 1954-1958 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - # 135 National Institute of Health A.J. Dalton, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - # 136 Yale University Henry Browning, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - # 137 University of Florida Francis E. Ray, 1954-1955 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - # 138 Vanderbilt University J. B. Youmans, 1954-1960 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - # 139 Yale University H.S. Fleming, 1954-1955 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - # 157 University of Athens Leonidas Zervas, 1956-1957 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - # 158 Middlesex Hospital M.A. Epstein, 1956-1960 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - # 159 St. Bartholomew's Hospital E.L. Kennaway, 1956-1958 (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - # 160 Yale University A.D. Welch, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - # 161 University of Glasgow J.N. Davidson, 1956-1958 (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - # 162 Yale University J.S. Nicholas, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - # 163 Tulane University E. T. Krementz, 1955-1963 (Box 11, Folder 82)
    - # 164 St. Bartholomew's Hospital--John W.S. Blacklock, 1956-1958 (Box 11, Folder 83)
    - # 165 Hebrew University E. Kargolissh. R Guttman, 1957-1960 (Box 11, Folder 84)
    - # 166 Netherlands Cancer Institute O. Huhlbock, 1958-1960 (Box 11, Folder 85)
    - # 167 Danish Cancer Registry Johannes Clemmesen, 1953-1963 (Box 11, Folder 86-87)
    - # 168 Cancer Research International Union Against Cancer (Box 11, Folder 88)
    - # 169 Yale University P.J. Thung, 1957-1959 (Box 11, Folder 89)
    - # 170 Yale University Leslie Foulds, 1956-1957 (Box 11, Folder 90)
    - # 171 University of Texas Robert B. Hurlbert, 1957-1959 (Box 11, Folder 91)
    - # 172 Yale University A.W. Gshtan, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 92)
    - # 173 University Institute of Pathological Anatomy, Copenhagen, Denmark Horten Simonsen, 1957-1959 (Box 12, Folder 93)
    - # 174 American University, Beirut, Lebanon John H. Schneider, 1957-1964 (Box 12, Folder 94-95)
    - # 175 Radiumstatfonen. Copenhagen Jorgen Rygaard, 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 96)
    - # 176 Yale University George Kalf, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 97)
    - # 177 National Cancer Institute G.C. Stelakatos, 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 9B)
    - # 178 Yale University F. Duran-Reynals, 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 99)
    - # 179 Netherlands Cancer Institute S. Kullander, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 100)
    - # 180 Centre de Recherche H.P. Bul Hoi, 1958-1961 (Box 12, Folder 101)
    - # 181 National Research Council, 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 102)
    - # 182 University of Illinois Harris Busch, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 103)
    - # 183 Radiumststionen Jorgen Rygaard, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 104)
    - # 185 University of Athens L. Zervas, 1958-1960 (Box 12, Folder 105)
    - # 186 University of Illinois E. Fujiwara, 1958-1960 (Box 12, Folder 106)
    - # 187 Yale University Thomas Lincoln, 1958-1959 (Box 12, Folder 107)
    - # 188 Netherlands Cancer Institute Anna Dux, 1958-1969 (Box 13, Folder 108)
    - # 189 Yale University w.e. Winternitz, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 109)
    - # 190 Yale University Akitsugu Ojima, 1958-1961 (Box 13, Folder 110)
    - # 191 Johns Hopkins University W.L. Nyhan, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 111)
    - # 192 New York Zoological Society Myron Gordon, 1958-1960 (Box 13, Folder 112)
    - # 193 California Institute of Technology Ray D. Owen, 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 113)
    - # 194 University of Witwatersrand. Johannesburg Joseph Gillman, 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 114)
    - # 195 Yale University Melvin V. Simpson, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 115)
    - # 196 Yale University Kazumasa Hoshino, 1959-1963 (Box 13, Folder 116)
    - # 197 Detroit Institute of Cancer Research Y. Hayashi, 1958-1961 (Box 13, Folder 117)
    - # 198 Bia Research Institute Peter C. Harpel, 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 118)
    - # 199 College de France Natalie Pourreau, 1959-1961 (Box 13, Folder 119-120)
    - # 200 Institute for Cancer Research Vithal Hitbander, 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 121)
    - # 201 South Africa Institute, Johannesburg, 1959-1960 (Box 14, Folder 122)
    - # 203 Anti-Cancer Council of Victoria (Australia) (Box 14, Folder 123)
    - # 204 Louisiana State University (Pharmacology), 1959-1960 (Box 14, Folder 124)
    - # 205 Yale University H.G. Klemperer, 1959-1963 (Box 14, Folder 125)
    - # 206 Israel Cancer Association G. Kallner, 1959-1963 (Box 14, Folder 126)
    - # 207 University of Western Australia R.E.J. ten Seldam, 1959-1964 (Box 14, Folder 127-128)
    - # 208 Yale University W. U. Gardner, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 129)
    - # 209 Hakerere College J.N.P. Davies, 1959-1963 (Box 14, Folder 130)
    - # 210 University of Southern California Paul Kotin, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 131)
    - # 211 Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn J.S. Bellin, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 132)
    - # 212 Baylor University Harry Busch, 1960-1964 (Box 14, Folder 133)
    - # 213 Yale University Donald F. King, 1960-1961 (Box 14, Folder 134)
    - # 214 Jefferson Medical College Dr. Hutchinson, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 135)
    - # 215 Stanford University R. Desai, 1960-1962 (Box 15, Folder 136)
    - # 216 Cairo Symposium International Union Against Cancer, 1958-1960 (Box 15, Folder 137)
    - # 217 Makerere College J.N.P. Davies, 1960-1963 (Box 15, Folder 138)
    - # 218 National Academy of Science International Intersociety Committee on Pathology, 1960-1962 (Box 15, Folder 139)
    - # 219 Baylor University Montague Lane, 1960-1961 (Box 15, Folder 140)
    - # 220 Tokyo Medical and Dental University Wataru Mori, 1960-1964 (Box 15, Folder 141)
    - # 221 International Union Against Cancer Kaposi Symposium, 1961-1962 (Box 15, Folder 142)
    - # 222 Oklahoma Medical Research Institute, 1960-1962 (Box 15, Folder 143)
    - # 223 Johns Hopkins University Earl Walker, 1961-1962 (Box 15, Folder 144)
    - # 224 University of Melbourne T.R. Bradley, S. Rose, 1961-1966 (Box 15, Folder 145)
    - # 225 University of Wisconsin Tetsuo Ono, 1957-1962 (Box 15, Folder 146)
    - # 226 USA National Committee International Union Against Cancer, 1961-1962 (Box 15, Folder 147)
    - # 227 Bland-Sutton Institute of Pathology R.M. Hicks, 1960-1966 (Box 16, Folder 148)
    - # 228 Kyushu University. Japan, 1961-1964 (Box 16, Folder 149)
    - # 229 Yale University J. Skoda, 1961-1963 (Box 16, Folder 150)
    - # 230 Mie Prefectural University, Japan Yasuaki Nishizuka, 1961-1965 (Box 16, Folder 151)
    - # 231 American Association Cancer Reserch: Skin Cancer, 1961-1962 (Box 16, Folder 152)
    - # 232 Jackson Memorial Hospital Miami, Florida, 1961-1966 (Box 16, Folder 153)
    - # 233 Rhodes University. S. Africa Rex Burrell, 1960-1967 (Box 16, Folder 154-155)
    - # 235 Brown University Paul Gross, 1962-1964 (Box 17, Folder 156)
    - # 236 National University. Paraguay Manuel Riveros, 1962-1965 (Box 17, Folder 157)
    - # 237 Baylor University E. Bresnick, 1962-1963 (Box 17, Folder 158)
    - # 238 Foundation for Advanced Education Alfredo Precerutti, 1962-1963 (Box 17, Folder 159)
    - # 239 Layoia University Joseph R. Davies, 1962-1963 (Box 17, Folder 160)
    - # 240 Yale University J. Rostgaard, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 161)
    - # 241 University of Western Ontario K. Hoshino, 1962-1963 (Box 17, Folder 162)
    - # 242 Gordon Research Conference Joseph Leighton, 1962-1963 (Box 17, Folder 163)
    - # 244 Chester Beatty Research Institute J. S. Harington, 1962-1963 (Box 17, Folder 164)
    - # 245 Universidad del Valle, Cali Colombia Pelayo Correa, 1962-1966 (Box 18, Folder 165-167)
    - # 246 Yale University Akirra Hizutani, 1963-1965 (Box 18, Folder 168)
    - # 247 American Institute for Cancer Research Alfred Gellhorn, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 169)
    - # 248 Yale University George Brawerman, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 170)
    - # 249 Albany Medical College J.N.P. Davies, 1962-1964 (Box 18, Folder 171)
    - # 250 Baylor University Audrey Fjelde, 1962-1963 (Box 18, Folder 172)
    - # 251 King George VI Hospital Peter Clifford, 1962-1967 (Box 18, Folder 173-175)
    - # 251 King George VI Hospital Chester Beatty Institute, 1952-1966 (Box 19, Folder 176)
    - # 252 Yale University Shiro Tsunamura, 1962-1964 (Box 19, Folder 177)
    - # 253 Yale University Stuart C. Finch, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 178)
    - # 254 Oak Ridge Biology Foundation C.C. Congdon, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 179)
    - # 255 Harvard Medical School John R. Blair-West, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 180)
    - # 256 Institute de Hematologt8 Alfredo S. Precerutti, 1963-1965 (Box 19, Folder 181)
    - # 257 Roswell Park Memorial Institute P.N. Raina, 1962-1965 (Box 19, Folder 182)
    - # 258 McGill University J.B. Fre!, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 183)
    - # 259 Yale University Louis Gluck, 1963-1965 (Box 19, Folder 184)
    - # 260 Yale University Y.S. Bakhle, 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 185)
    - # 261 National Research Council Allen Cheever, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 186)
    - # 262 International Union Against Cancer Geographical Pathology, 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 187)
    - # 263 Yale University Fred Prince, 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 188)
    - # 264 Baylor University Raoul Desjardins, 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 189)
    - # 266 University of Edinburgh J.E. Cummins, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 190)
    - # 267 Yale University Charles E. Graham, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 191)
    - # 268 International Union Against Cancer Asbestos, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 192-193)
    - # 269 Rockefeller Institute Edward Reich, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 194)
    - # 270 Foundation for Advancement of Education Guy de The, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 195)
    - # 271 University of Pennsylvania Scientists in Medical Research, 1964-1968 (Box 20, Folder 196)
    - # 272 Foundation for Advancement of Education Makato Hori, 1964-1966 (Box 20, Folder 197)
    - # 273 Wakayama College Ueda Gaiko, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 198)
    - # 274 Yale University A.B. Lerne, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 199)
    - # 275 Union Internationale Contre le Cancer H. Mitchell Project, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 200)
    - # 276 Yale University Ira S. Goldenberg, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 201)
    - # 277 University of Oslo D.H. Iverson, 1962-1965 (Box 20, Folder 202)
    - # 278 Institute of Oncology W. Bartoszewicz, 1964-1968 (Box 20, Folder 203)
    - # 279 Postgraduate Medical School, Budapest K. Lapis, 1964-1968 (Box 20, Folder 204-205)
    - # 281 Kansai Medical School Kazuo Ogawa, 1964-1967 (Box 20, Folder 206)
    - # 283 McGill University J.D. McDonald, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 207)
    - # 284 Foundation for Advanced Education Francesco Mauro, 1964-1967 (Box 21, Folder 208)
    - # 285 Karolinska Institute Geoffrey Rau, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 209)
    - # 286 Yale University W. B. Radcliffe, 1965-1967 (Box 21, Folder 210)
    - # 287 Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 211)
    - # 288 Mount Sinai Hospital I.J. Selikoff, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 212)
    - # 289 Howard University La Salle D. Leffell, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 213)
    - # 291 Chester Beatty Research Institute, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 214)
    - # 292 Karolinska Institute Elli Kohen, 1965-1967 (Box 21, Folder 215-216)
    - # 293 University of Ibadan Frances Mattram, 1965-1970 (Box 22, Folder 217)
    - # 294 Walter and Eliza Hall Institute of Medical Research J.F.A.P. Hiller, 1965-1967 (Box 22, Folder 218)
    - # 295 University of Perugis, 1965-1969 (Box 22, Folder 219)
    - # 296 Sever! and Biancifiori University of Perugis F. Squarein!, 1965-1969 (Box 22, Folder 220)
    - # 297 IX International Cancer Congress, Tokyo, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 221)
    - # 298 Foundation for the Advancement of Education Victor Bedoys, 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 222)
    - # 299 Central Hospital. Kuopio. Finland L.O. Meurman, 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 223)
    - # 300 Yale University Gisela Turck, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 224)
    - # 301 University of Florida Gisela Turck Cramer, 1967-1969 (Box 22, Folder 225)
    - # 302 International Union Against Cancer, 1965-1967 (Box 22, Folder 226)
    - # 303 Manhattan College Jaques Lipeu, 1965-1967 (Box 23, Folder 227)
    - # 303 University of Toronto, 1965-1967 (Box 23, Folder 228)
    - # 304 Kyushu University Ryosaburo Takaki, 1955-1966 (Box 23, Folder 229)
    - # 305 Yale University E.S. Canellakis, 1966-1968 (Box 23, Folder 230)
    - # 306 National Cancer Center, Tokyo Takashi Yamada, 1966-1969 (Box 23, Folder 231)
    - # 307 Institute of Child Health Evangelos Kaslaris, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 232)
    - # 308 American University Paul A. Woke, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 233)
    - # 309 Fund for Advancement of Education Peter Fortnagel, 1966-1968 (Box 23, Folder 234)
    - # 310 Institut de Recherches, Villejuif, France Danld-Slatkin, 1966-1969 (Box 23, Folder 235)
    - # 311 University of Kansas J K. Frenkel, 1966-1971 (Box 23, Folder 236)
    - # 312 Pan American Health G. Wynne Griffith, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 237)
    - # 313 Yale University Eduardo Dominguez, 1966-1969 (Box 23, Folder 238)
    - # 314 Yale University Gerda Tyrsted, 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 239)
    - # 315 University of Texas Walter J. Burdette, 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 240)
    - # 316 Free University of Berlin Gerhard R. Kruger, 1966-1969 (Box 24, Folder 241)
    - # 317 Queen's University Bernardo Pinto, 1966-1969 (Box 24, Folder 242)
    - # 318 University of Freiburg Gerhard Schreiber, 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 243)
    - # 319 Yale University Averill Liebow, 1966-1969 (Box 24, Folder 244)
    - # 321 Western Reserve University Joseph E. Cummins, 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 245)
    - # 322 Salk Institute Melvin Cohn, 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 246)
    - # 323 University of Melbourne T.R. Bradley, 1966-1968 (Box 24, Folder 247)
    - # 324 Institute for Muscle Disease. Inc. Armand Tavitlan, 1967-1969 (Box 24, Folder 248)
    - # 325 University of Tokyo Yoshitake Mana, 1966-1970 (Box 25, Folder 249)
    - # 326 Massachusetts Institute of Technology W.A. Anderson, 1967-1970 (Box 25, Folder 250)
    - # 327 Trinity College. Ireland Dermot Twomey, 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder 251)
    - # 328 Sasaki Institute Department of Biochemistry, 1968-1972 (Box 25, Folder 252)
    - # 329 University of California, Berkeley Marc A. Lappe, 1968-1970 (Box 25, Folder 253)
    - # 330 MRC Laboratory of Molecular Biology. University Postgraduate Medical School, Cambridge England, 1968-1969 (Box 25, Folder 254)
    - # 331 Yale University S. Clayman. A.C. Sartorelli, 1967-1970 (Box 25, Folder 255)
    - # 359 Temple University. Philadelphia Marvin Sodicoff, 1970-1972 (Box 25, Folder 256)
    - # 361 University of Birmingham Henry P. Godfrey, 1970-1973 (Box 25, Folder 257)
    - # 362 University of Toronto J .A. Kellen, 1970-1974 (Box 26, Folder 258)
    - # 363 Georgetown University Kathryn V. Holmes, 1970-1972 (Box 26, Folder 259)
    - # 364 Dartmouth Medical School Marilynn Waite, 1970-1973 (Box 26, Folder 260)
    - # 365 Howard University S.K. Dutta, 1970-1972 (Box 26, Folder 261-262)
    - # 369 Washington University, St. Louis, Missouri Phillip Stahl, 1971-1973 (Box 26, Folder 263)
    - # 372 Theagenion Cancer Institute J. Taylor-Papadlmltrlau, 1971-1973 (Box 26, Folder 264)
    - # 373 University of Pennsylvania Eugene M. Edynak, 1971-1973 (Box 26, Folder 265)
    - # 374 University of North Carolina James D. Folds, 1971-1973 (Box 26, Folder 266)
    - # 375 University of Auckland, New Zealand A.R. Bellamy, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 267)
    - # 376 Harvard Medical School C.W. Pierce, 1971-1973 (Box 27, Folder 268)
    - # 377 Yale Medical School Gerard H. Burrow, 1971-1973 (Box 27, Folder 269)
    - # 378 Yale Medical School T.E. Donnelly, 1971-1973 (Box 27, Folder 270)
    - # 379 Harvard School of Public Health M.E. Essex, 1971-1973 (Box 27, Folder 271)
    - # 380 Medical College of Pennsylvania Barbara Zajac, 1971-1973 (Box 27, Folder 272)
    - # 381 Yale University John M. Pawelek, 1971-1973 (Box 27, Folder 273)
    - # 382 Yale University David S. Papermaster, 1972-1974 (Box 27, Folder 274)
    - # 383 Louisiana State University Henry Rothschild, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 275)
    - # 384 Yale University 0.0. Odujinrin, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 276)
    - # 385 University of Wisconsin H.R. Schinltsky, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 277)
    - # 386 Stanford University Medical Center, 1972-1975 (Box 27, Folder 278)
    - # 387 Harvard University Terry A. Beerman, 1972-1974 (Box 28, Folder 279)
    - # 388 Veterans Administration Carlo Koscovici, 1972-1974 (Box 28, Folder 280)
    - # 389 Hebrew University Gury Zvilichoysky, 1972-1976 (Box 28, Folder 281)
    - # 390 De La Recherche Scientifique Joseph Fonda Mais!n, 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 282)
    - # 391 Wdter and-E112:3 Hall Institute Jerry M. Adams, 1972-1975 (Box 28, Folder 283)
    - # 392 Massachusetts Institute of Technology M.J. McDowell, 1972-1976 (Box 28, Folder 284)
    - # 393 Walter and Eliza Hall Institute John J. Marchalonis, 1972-1975 (Box 28, Folder 285)
    - # 394 Washington State University Howard L. Hosick, 1972-1974 (Box 28, Folder 286)
    - # 395 Yale University Daniel M. Albert. Ted W. Reid, 1972-74 (Box 28, Folder 287)
    - # 396 University of California James A. Robb, 1973-1977 (Box 28, Folder 288)
    - # 397 Yale University J. Schenckman, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 289)
    - # 398 Clinical Research Council R. Diamond, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 290)
    - # 399 Howard University R. Humphreys, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 291)
    - # 400 Albany Medical College James McSherry, 1973-1975 (Box 28, Folder 292)
    - # 401 University of Oregon Elizabeth A. Eipper, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 293)
    - # 402 University of California Peter R. Shank, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 294)
    - # 404 Daphne Kamely: Declined, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 295)
    - # 405 Patrick Chung Shu Kung: Declined, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 296)